Dylan Wong

Software Developer, Web Designer, Math & Computer Science Major

(775) 857-7906 dylanwong@nevada.unr.edu www.wong-innovations.me www.github.com/wong-innovations

EXPERIENCE

Fox Optimization, Reno NV − QA Intern

DECEMBER 2018 - PRESENT

Writing code to test the functionality of Fox Optimization's scheduling application. Bug finding, UX enhancing, and functionality verification.

Scraps Dog Company, Sparks NV — Sales Associate

JUNE 2014 - PRESENT

Providing knowledgeable service to caring animal owners, carrying out transactions, and website management for the company.

EDUCATION

School Name, Location — B.S. in Math & Computer Science

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

I am currently a freshman pursuing my Bachelor's in both Mathematics and Computer Science.

PROJECTS

Hackathons — Competitive Coding

Hackathons are a great test of one's collaboration and coding abilities, as a category winner of the 2018 ACM Hackathon, I am no stranger to the hard work required to complete a project in a tight deadline.

Data Mining — Scraping The Web

Humans have created more data in the past year than in the entirety of history before it, the interface between companies and this valuable data is lacking to say the least. Using Selenium and APIs I have began to collect valuable data that companies can use for more effective marketing.

Cybersecurity — Data Protection

I am taking online course towards a cybersecurity certification, with cyber attacks occuring every three seconds globally, both software developers and web designers need to have the knowledge to code defensively.

HARD SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript
SQL and NOSQL databases
C++ and Python app development
Adobe Suite and MS Office
APIs, Frameworks, and Libraries
Graphic Design, UI, UX

SOFT SKILLS

Communication

Organization

Accountability

Adaptability

Problem Solving

Work Ethic

SUMMARY

I am a highly motivated individual with a love for learning and problem solving. I have experience in a multitude of programming languages and constantly challenge myself to grow and learn. Both physically and academically, I've never been known to back down from a challenge. I love meeting and working with equally motivated individuals.